SEAN MILFORT

Harrisburg, PA | 732-675-1755

www.seanmilfort.com | seanmilfort@me.com

Summary

System Administrator with experience in handling multiple different Operating Systems (Windows, macOS, Linux, Android & iOS) in a fast pace and growing environment. Personable employee with a strong background in handling multiple tasks & customer service. Always ready for a challenge.

Work Experience

WellSpan Health | York, PA System Administrator **December 2019 - Present**

December 2019 - Present

- Creating/Developing Application Packages & Software Installations for mass/minor deployments
- Creating Technical/Support Documentation for new & existing solutions
- Evaluating/Designing Technical Solutions to improve End User Workflow
- Developing/Troubleshooting Mobile Device Management Solutions (AirWatch)
- Maintaining/Improving IT Environment with new Technological Improvements

Burlington Stores, Inc. | Burlington, NJ *IT Integration Analyst II*

April 2015 – November 2019

November 2017 – November 2019

- Created Installer/Scripting Packages for silent installations for 15,000 Machine (Unix Scripting, PowerShell & Bash)
- Developed/Maintained the Base Computer Image for 4,000+ machines (Windows/Mac)
- Created/Edited/Deployed Group Policy 15,000+ active devices
- Responsible for large-scale Engineering/Design changes to our Mobile Device Management Platform (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ devices (iOS, Android & Windows CE)
- Evaluated/Met with Senior Business Partners/Vendors on multiple different initiatives

Key Achievements: Re-engineered/designed Current mobile device Management System, Received CIO Award for teamwork/collaboration

IT Integration Analyst I

April 2017 – November 2017

- Implemented/Led Microsoft Surface Project in Corporate/Field Environment
- Planned/Integrated New Technology into Current Environment
- Maintained/Deployed Bi-Quarterly Updates to 4,000+ Machines
- Handled Maintenance/Support/Upgrades of Mobile Device Management Product (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ active devices
- Researched/Suggested Solutions to improve Productivity/Performance

Key Achievements: Implemented Microsoft Surfaces into Corporate Environment

- Helped Create/Set the company standard for Corporate Level Devices (Windows/Mac)
- Created Mobile profiles and packages for iOS Devices in Corporate/Store Environment for 4,000+ Mobile Devices
- Authored/Maintained Support and Procedural Documentation for Support Teams
- Created/Deployed Software Packages on large scale for Endpoints (Windows/Mac)

Key Achievements: Received CEO Award for providing excellent support for remote sites for regional meetings

Client Technologies Technician I

April 2015 – October 2016

- Supported/Troubleshooted Windows and Mac Machines on a large scale
- Participated in many different with various projects with different departments in IT
- Supported Mobile Devices (iPad and iPhones) while utilizing AirWatch as MDM tool
- Basic Network troubleshooting and configuration (DNS, VLAN, Connectivity)
- Delivered Customer Service to Troubleshoot and Enhance End User Experience

Key Achievements: Configured all macOS machines in Corporate Environment to meet company standard (50+ machines)

EDUCATION

La Salle University, Expected Graduation in 2021
Master of Science (M.S.), Computer Information Science

Philadelphia, PA

La Salle University, 2015
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Computer Science

Philadelphia, PA

SKILLS

- Programming: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Swift, Bash, PowerShell
- Operating Systems: Windows, macOS, iOS, Linux, Android
- Infrastructure Skills: Patch Management, Mobile Device Management (AirWatch), OS Management, Microsoft Deployment Toolkit (MDT), Active Directory & Group Policy Management, Large Scale Software Packaging & Deployment (IBM BigFix & Symantec Altiris)
- Interpersonal Skills: Customer Service, Teamwork, Leadership, Communication, Technical Documentation